

22. Princess Residence (22B-01).
Jalan Raja Mahmud.
50300 Kampung Baru.
Kuala Lumpur
+60 19-779 9074
aisyahhanifiah@live.com

PROFILE

Name: Nur Aisyah binti Mohd Hanifiah Date of Birth: 16 April 1996 IC: 960416-10-6422

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I find joy in creating visuals that are able to engage with people effectively while fulfilling the aesthetics of each graphic element. Based on my past experiences being a graphic designer. I learnt a lot about how each graphics and type could influence the viewers. It is that everywhere I go I would think to myself on how people could improve their marketing materials. I also do work well both as a member of a team and in isolation with high attention to detail.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Amber & Sparkles | Sept 2016 - Dec 2016

- Creating graphics based on tasks given and meeting deadlines
- Developed a strong attention to details towards each task.

FREELANCE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

The Pixel Things | August 2016 - current

- Founder of The Pixel Things (Instagram: @thepixelthings)
- Manage projects, customers and meeting deadlines

INDUSTRIAL TRAINING

Motive Interactive Sdn, Bhd. | Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

- Assist in software development cycles for ongoing projects.
- Developed personal project using Laravel PHP framework
- http://leave-management-system.motive.com.my/dashboard

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Universiti Kuala Lumpur (MIIT) | June 2014 - June 2017 CGPA: 3.97

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2012 - 2013

Pure science

Grade: 5A+ 4A

PENILAIAN MENENGAH RENDAH

Sekolah Tun Fatimah | 2009-2011

Grade: 8A

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator PHP HTML & CSS WordPress Bootstrap MySQL

KNOWLEDGE

JAVA C# C++ VB.NET ASP.NET

PERSONAL SKILLS

TEAMWORK

CREATIVITY

ORGANIZATION

COMMUNICATION

INDEPENDENT

REFERENCES

NORHATTA BINTI MOHD | Academic Advisor +60 12-209 3859 | norhatta@unikl.edu.my

MUHAMMAD ASHRAF BIN ROSLAN | Amber & Sparkles +60 18-663 7097 | order.amberandsparkles@qmail.com

NURUL HIDAYAH HASAN BASRI | Motive Interactive Sdn Bhd +603 2714 5689 | hidayah@motive.com.my

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Malay English